(Earth rumbling)
(title ringing)
(radio chattering)
(dramatic music)
[Reproducció de música]
[音樂播放]
[μουσική]
[Zenelejátszás]
[Memutar Musik]
[Riproduzione di musica]
[音楽の演奏]
♪
[Muzyka]
[Redarea muzicii]
[Музыка играет]
[เล่นดนตรี]
[Müzik çalıyor]
(ISS whooshing)
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
♪ Komm und fahr mit ♪
♪ Venha e faça um passeio grátis ♪
♪ Vamos y toma un viaje gratis ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ sim, sim, sim, sim ♪
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
♪ Komm und fahr mit ♪
♪ Venha e faça um passeio grátis ♪
♪ Vamos y toma un viaje gratis ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ sim, sim, sim, sim ♪
Commandant.
أيها القائد
Comandant
指揮官。
Veliteli
Κυβερνήτη.
Parancsnok.
Komandan.
Comandante.
船長
함장.
Komandorze.
Comandant.
Commander.
ท่านผู้นำ
Komutan.
- Commander, we are good for pre-flight.
- Commander, die Vorflugkontrolle war erfolgreich.
- Comandante, estamos prontos para o pré-vôo.
- Comandante, todo está bien para el pre-vuelo.
Prêts pour la phase prévol.
جاهزون للرحلة الاستباقية
Estem a punt per la verificació prèvia.
我們很適合飛行前。
Jsme dobří na předlet.
Έτοιμοι για διαδικασία ελέγχων πτήσης.
Jó vagyunk a repülés előtt.
Kami baik-baik saja untuk pra-penerbangan.
Siamo pronti per il pre-volo.
全て正常よ
Jesteśmy gotowi na pierwszy lot
Suntem buni pentru pre-zbor.
Мы готовы для предполетного полета.
เราเตรียมดีแล้วสำหรับการบินล่วงหน้า
Uçuş öncesi için iyiyiz.
비행 전 테스트 준비가 됐네.
- [Ethan] Roger that.
- [Ethan] Roger.
- [Ethan] Ok.
- [Ethan] Enterado.
Bien reçu.
عُلم
Entesos.
收到。
Rozumím.
Ελήφθη.
Értettem.
Diterima.
Ricevuto.
了解。
확인.
Potwierdzam.
Recepționat.
Заметано.
รับทราบ.
Anlaşıldı.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ sim, sim, sim, sim ♪
Télémétrie finale en cours de téléchargement.
استعد لرفع وتثبيت الإحداثيات النهائية
En espera per la darrera càrrega de telemetria.
待機進行最後的遙測 上傳和鎖定。
Pohotovostní režim pro konečnou telemetrii nahrát a zamknout.
Αναμείνατε για τελική φόρτωση τηλεμετρίας και ρυθμίσεων.
Készenléti állapot a végső telemetriához feltöltés és zárolás.
Siaga untuk unggah telemetri akhir dan kunci.
Standby per telemetria finale caricata e pronta.
最終遠隔測定を受信するまでそのまま待機して。
최종 원격측정기 장착 및 고정을 준비하게.
Jesteśmy gotowi do przesłania i zablokowania ostatniej telemetrii
Așteptați pentru telemetria finală încărcați și blocați.
Резерв для окончательной телеметрии загрузить и заблокировать.
สแตนด์บายสำหรับการอัปโหลดและล็อก telemetry ขั้นตอนสุดท้าย
Son telemetri için bekleme yükle ve kilitle.
- Standby for final telemetry upload and lock.
- Standby für finalen Telemetrie-Upload und Verschluss.
- Prontos para o upload final e bloqueio de telemetria.
- En espera para la última carga de telemetría y bloqueo.
Oh, and the crew hope you're enjoying
Oh und die Crew hofft, dass Ihnen
Ah, e a tripulação espera que você esteja gostando
Oh, el equipo espera que estés disfrutando
امم وأيضاً
Ah, i ...
哦，還有......
A, a ...
Α ! Και...
Ó, és ...
Oh, dan ...
Oh e...
ええっと、それと…
오, 그리고...
O, i...
Oh si...
Ох и ...
โอ้ และ ...
Oh ve...
L'équipe espère que la musique vous plaît.
الطاقم يتمنى لك الاستمتاع بالموسيقى المُختارة لك
L'equip espera que estigueu gaudint de la serenata de partida.
船員們希望你們享受 你發送的小夜曲。
Posádka doufá, že se těšíte Vaše vysílací serenáda.
Το πλήρωμα ελπίζει να είσαι ευχαριστημένος με την μουσική...
A legénység reméli, hogy élvezed küldje el a serenádot.
Awak berharap kau menikmati serenade pengiriman Anda.
L'equipaggio spera che ti stia divertendo con la tua serenata di saluto.
クルーのみんなは、あなたの送別会を楽しんでいたわよ。
팀원들이 자네 송별곡이 마음에 들었으면 좋겠다는군.
Załoga ma nadzieję, że się cieszysz z przesłanej serenady.
Echipajul speră că te bucuri trimiteți-vă serenada.
Экипаж надеюсь, что вы наслаждаетесь твоей серенадой
ทีมงานหวังว่าคุณจะสนุกไปกับเซเรเนดของคุณน่ะ
Sevdiğin mürettebat umudu senden serenat gönder.
your send off serenade.
Ihr Abschiedslied gefällt.
da serenata de despedida.
tu serenata de lanzamiento.
ผมอยากเจอมนุษย์ต่างดาวจังเลย
♪ Yeah, yeah, ooh, hoo ♪
♪ Sim, sim, ooh, hoo ♪
- It's perfect, thank you.
- Es ist perfekt, danke.
- É perfeito, obrigado.
- Es perfecta, gracias.
C'est parfait, merci.
إنها مثالية، شكراً لكم
És perfecte, gràcies.
這是完美的，謝謝。
Perfektní, děkuji.
Είναι τέλεια, ευχαριστώ.
Tökéletes, köszönöm.
Sempurna, terima kasih.
È perfetto, grazie.
バッチリだ。ありがとう。
하하. 완벽합니다. 고마워요.
Jest idealna, dziękuję.
Este perfect, mulțumesc.
Это прекрасно, спасибо.
มันสมบูรณ์แบบแล้วขอบคุณ
Mükemmel, teşekkürler.
- [Sarah] Thought you'd like it.
- [Sarah] Dachte ich mir.
- [Sarah] Achei que você gostaria disso.
- [Sarah] Pensé que te gustaría.
On s'en doutait.
اعتقدنا أنها ستعجبك.
Hem pensat que us agradaria.
我們以為你會喜歡它。
Mysleli jsme, že byste to chtěl.
Το ξέραμε πως θα σου αρέσει.
Azt hittük, szeretné.
Kami pikir kau akan menyukainya.
Abbiamo pensato che ti sarebbe piaciuto.
そういうと思ったわ。
좋아할 줄 알았네.
Sądzimy, że ci się spodoba.
Am crezut că ți-ar plăcea.
Мы думали, тебе понравится.
พวกเราคิดว่าคุณจะชอบมันน่ะ
Hoşuna gider diye düşündük.
♪ Take a free ride ♪ - Standby for final checks
♪ Fahr mit ♪ - Standby für finale Checks
♪ Faça um passeio grátis ♪ - Esperando as verificações
♪ Toma un viaje gratis ♪ -En espera para las últimas ♪
استعد للفحوص النهائية وتجربة الاتصالات
En espera per les comprovacions finals i les proves de transmissió.
待機進行最終檢查 和傳輸測試。
Pohotovostní kontrola a přenosových zkoušek.
Αναμείνατε για τελικούς ελέγχους και αποστολή στοιχείων.
Készenléti állapot a végső ellenőrzésekhez és átviteli tesztek.
Siaga untuk pemeriksaan terakhir dan tes transmisi.
Standby per i controlli finali e test di trasmissione.
最終チェック、それと”転送”テストの準備。
최종 점검과 송수신 테스트를 준비하게.
Przygotuj się na ostatnie sprawdzenie i testy transmisji.
Așteptare pentru verificări finale și testele de transmisie.
Резерв для окончательных проверок и тесты трансмиссии.
สแตนด์บายสำหรับการตรวจสอบขั้นสุดท้ายและการทดสอบการส่งสัญญาณน่ะ
Son kontroller için bekleme ve iletim testleri.
Dernières vérifications en cours.
and transmission tests.
und Übertragungstests.
e testes de transmissão.
revisiones y pruebas de transmisión.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ sim, sim, sim, sim ♪
Cinq sur cinq, Contrôle. Prêt au désengagement.
عشرة على عشرة مركز التحكم، جاهز للانفصال.
Cinc per cinc, Control. A punt per desacoblar.
五點五，飛行。 準備脫離。
Pět z pěti, loď připravena k odpojení.
Πέντε στα πέντε, Κέντρο. Έτοιμος προς αποσύνδεση
Öt öt, Repülés. Készen áll a kikapcsolásra.
Lima kali lima, Penerbangan. Siap melepaskan diri.
Fly by wire, Volo. Pronto a sganciare.
手順５/５、分離準備完了。
모두 양호하다, 플라이트. 분리 준비 완료
5 na 5, Kontrola. Gotowy do rozłączenia.
Cinci pe cinci, Zborul. Sunteți pregătit să vă dezactivați.
Пять на пять, Рейс. Готовы отключиться.
ห้าต่อห้าเที่ยวบิน พร้อมที่จะปลดประจำการแล้วคับ
Beşe beş, Uçuş. Ayrılmaya hazır.
- Five by five, Flight.
- Fünf von fünf, Flight.
- Cinco por cinco, vôo.
- Cinco en cinco, vuelo.
Ready to disengage.
Bereit für Loslösung.
Pronto para desengatar.
Listo para desengancharse.
- Proceed.
- Fahren Sie fort.
- Prossiga.
- Procede.
Allez-y.
تقدم.
Procediu.
繼續。
Pokračovat.
Συνεχίστε.
Folytassa.
Memproses.
Procedere.
続行。
진행하게.
Kontynuować.
Continua.
Приступить.
ดำเนินการ
İlerlemek.
(dramatic music)
You are cleared for initial trust.
Alles klar für den Abflug.
Você está pronto para o passo inicial.
Estás despejado para el impulso inicial.
Ελεύθερος για αρχική πρόωση.
يمكنك إجراء الدفع الموجه الأول.
Esteu autoritzat per a l'impuls inicial.
您已獲得初始信任。
Jste připraveni na počáteční důvěru.
Az első bizalomért törlődik.
Kau diizinkan untuk kepercayaan awal.
Sei autorizzato per la manovra iniziale.
皆あなたを信じてるわ。
최초 점화를 허가한다.
Masz zgodę na uruchomienie silników.
Sunteți eliberați pentru încredere inițială.
Вы готовы для первоначальной инициализации.
คุณถูกล้างเพื่อความไว้วางใจครั้งแรก
İlk güven için onay aldınız.
Poussée initiale autorisée.
Bien reçu.
عُلم ذلك.
Entesos.
收到。
Rozumím.
Értettem.
Diterima.
Ricevuto.
了解。
확인.
Przyjąłem.
Recepționat.
Заметано.
รับทราบครับ
Anlaşıldı.
Ελήφθη.
- Roger that, moving out, quarter impulse.
- Roger, fliege mit einem Viertel Impuls los.
- Sim, saindo, quarto impulso.
- Enterado, saliendo, cuarto de impulso.
جاري التقدم، رُبع الدفع.
Sortint. A ¼ de l'impuls.
搬出去。四分之一的衝動。
Přemisťuji se. Čtvrtletní impuls.
Kiköltözni. Negyedik impulzus.
Pindah. Impuls seperempat.
Mi sto muovendo. Quarto d'impulso.
クォーターインパルス、離脱する。
출발한다. 4분의 1 출력.
Wychodzę. 1/4 impulsowej.
Mutarea. Impulsul trimestrial.
Выезжая. четверть импульса.
ย้ายออก แรงกระตุ้นไตรมาส
Taşınmak. Çeyrek dürtü.
Έξοδος. Παλμός 45 μοιρών.
Poussée, 1/4.
Espèce de nerd !
أيها الفظ
Setciències!
書呆子！
Nerd!
Kockafejû!
Kutu buku!
Nerd!
덕후자식!
Tocilar!
Ботан!
เนิร์ด!
İnek!
Σπασίκλα!
- [Sarah] Nerd!
[Sarah] ¡Nerd!
Et fier de l'être.
أحمل بطاقة "تعبير أجنبي كناية عن انضمامه لنادي أو جهة، هنا يقصد نادي الناس ذو التعامل الفظ"
Pixatintes.
卡攜帶。
Přenášení dat.
Μεταφορά δεδομένων.
Kártya szállítása.
Membawa kartu.
Porta carte
성공한 덕질이지.
Pełnoprawny.
Carte de transport.
Карта использована.
ถือบัตรไว้
Kart taşıma.
- Card carrying.
- Eingetragen.
- Cartão carregando.
- Portando tarjeta.
Vous avez intérêt à dire "ainsi soit-il" ou je serai déçu.
وإن لم تقولي "قم بعمله" سأصاب بخيبة أمل كبيرة
如果你不說“做到這一點”， 我會非常失望的。
A pokud neříkáte "udělej tak", Budu velmi zklamán.
Και αν δεν μου πεις "Καλή επιτυχία" θα απογοητευτώ πολύ.
És ha nem mondod, hogy "csináld így", Nagyon csalódni fogok.
Dan jika kamu tidak mengatakan "buat begitu", Aku akan sangat kecewa.
E se non dici "Fallo così", Sarò molto deluso.
ここに来て中止なんて言わないよな？
"증명해 봐."라고 받아쳐주지 않는다면 실망할 것 같은데.
I jeśli nie powiesz "zrób tak", Będę bardzo rozczarowany.
Și dacă nu spui "fă-o așa", Voi fi foarte dezamăgit.
И если вы не говорите «сделай так», Я буду очень разочарован.
และถ้าคุณไม่พูดว่า "ทำอย่างนั้น" ผมจะผิดหวังมาก
Ve eğer "öyle yap" demezseniz, Çok hayal kırıklığına uğradım.
I si no em dius "fes-ho", estaré molt decebut.
And if you don't say make it so,
Und wenn Sie nicht mach es so sagen,
E se você não disser isso,
Y si no dices hazlo así,
I'll be very disappointed.
werde ich sehr entäuscht sein.
eu ficarei muito desapontado.
estaré muy decepcionado.
C'est noté.
Anotat, comandant.
عُلم أيها القائد
注意到，指揮官。
Všimněte si, veliteli.
Το σημειώνω αυτό Κυβερνήτη.
Megjegyezte, parancsnok.
Tercatat, komandan.
Annotato, comandante.
お手並み拝見ね、船長。
기억해두지, 함장.
Zanotowano, komandorze
Atenție, comandant.
Отметил, командир.
เตรียมตั้งสังเกตการครับ ผู้บัญชาการ
Kaydetti, komutan.
- [Sarah] Noted, Commander.
- [Sarah] Notiert, Commander.
- [Sarah] Anotado, Comandante.
Procédez jusqu'au point d'allumage moteur.
من فضلك تقدم إلى نقطة استعداد المحرك
Procediu al punt d'iniciació.
請繼續 推動啟動點。
Pokračujte prosím k zadanemu bodu.
Προχωρήστε στο σημείο έναρξης υπερταχύτητας.
Kérjük, indítsa el az indítási pont meghajtása.
Silakan lanjutkan untuk mengarahkan titik inisiasi.
Procedere verso il punto d' inizio.
そのままワープ位置まで進んで。
드라이브 시동 지점으로 이동하게.
Proszę kontynuować do punktu startu.
Vă rog continuați pentru a conduce punctul de inițiere.
Пожалуйста, продолжайте прохождение начальной точки.
โปรดดำเนินการกับจุดเริ่มต้นการขับยาน
Lütfen devam et başlangıç ​​noktası sürmek için.
Please proceed to drive initiation point.
Bitte fahren Sie mit Abflugbeginn fort.
Por favor, avance até o ponto de iniciação.
Por favor procede a dirigir el punto de iniciación.
En route.
في الطريق
Ara mateix.
我在途中。
Jsem na cestě.
Είμαι καθ' οδόν.
Úton vagyok.
Dalam perjalanan.
Sulla mia rotta.
移動中。
갑니다.
Jestem w drodze.
Pe drum.
В пути.
ระหว่างทางของฉัน
Yolumun üzerinde.
- On my way.
- Bin dabei.
- Estou indo.
- En camino.
À très vite.
أراكم قريباً
Fins aviat.
再見。
Brzy se uvidíme.
Τα λέμε σύντομα.
Hamarosan találkozunk.
Sampai jumpa lagi.
A presto.
また会おう。
곧 갈게.
Do zobaczenia wkrótce.
Ne vedem în curând.
До скорой встречи.
แล้วค่อยพบกันเร็ว ๆ นี้
Yakında görüşürüz.
See you soon.
Bis bald.
Até logo.
Nos vemos pronto.
Quelle flèche !
اممم، سريع جداً
Ah, ets tan ràpid!
啊，這麼快！
Ach, tak rychle!
Α, είσαι τόσο γρήγορος !
Ah, olyan gyorsan!
Ah, sangat cepat!
Ah, così veloce!
ああ、速いわね！
와, 빠른걸!
Ach, i to szybko!
Ah, atât de repede!
Ах, так быстро!
โอ้ เร็วจัง!
Ah, çok hızlı!
- Ah, he's so fast!
- Ah, er ist so schnell!
- Ah, ele é tão rápido!
- Ah, ¡el es muy rápido!
(mellow music)
Someone's excited.
Da ist aber jemand aufgeregt.
Alguém está animado.
Alguien está emocionado.
J'en connais un qui trépigne.
أحد ما فرح جداً
Algú està entusiasmat.
有人很興奮。
Někdo je nadšený.
Είναι πολύ ενθουσιασμένος.
Valaki izgatott.
Seseorang bersemangat.
Qualcuno è eccitato.
誰かさんが興奮してるわね？
누구씨는 신났네.
Ktoś jest podekscytowany.
Cineva este încântat.
Кто-то взволнован.
มีคนตื่นเต้น
Birisi heyecanlı.
Tu as hâte de jouer avec ton nouveau joujou ?
أراك تنتظر أن تلعب بلعبتك الجديدة أليس كذلك ؟
Estàs desitjant jugar amb la teva nova joguina, oi?
你期待著比賽 用你的新玩具，不是嗎？
Těšíte se na hraní s vaší novou hračkou, ne?
Ανυπομονείς να παίξεις με το καινούργιο σου παιχνίδι, έτσι ;
Várjuk a játékot az új játékkal, ugye?
KAmu tak sabar untuk bermain dengan mainan barumu, bukan?
Non vedi l'ora di giocare con il tuo nuovo giocattolo, vero?
あなたは遊ぶのを楽しみにしている、 あなたの新しいおもちゃで、そうでしょ？
새 장난감 갖고 놀 생각에 신났지?
Nie możesz się doczekać zabawy Twoją nową zabawką, prawda?
Așteptăm cu nerăbdare să jucăm cu noua jucărie, nu-i așa?
Вы с нетерпением ждете возможности поиграть с вашей новой игрушкой, не так ли?
คุณตั้งตาคอยที่จะเล่นกับของเล่นใหม่ใช่ไหม?
Oynamak için can atıyorsun Yeni oyuncağınla değil mi?
You're looking forward to playing
Freust du dich darauf,
Você está ansioso para jogar
¿Estás esperando jugar
with your new toy, Commander?
mit deinem neuen Spielzeug zu spielen, Commander?
com seu novo brinquedo, comandante?
con tu nuevo juguete, Comandante?
Oui, mais n'ébruite pas qu'on l'appelle "mon joujou".
نعم، ولكن لا تخبريهم أننا نسميها "لعبتي"
Ho estic, però potser que no els diguis que l'anomenem "la meva joguina".
我是，但也許不要告訴他們 我們稱之為“我的玩具”。
Já jsem, ale možná jim to neříkej, říkáme "moje hračka".
Ε ναι, αλλά μην τους πεις ότι το αποκαλούμε παιχνίδι.
Én vagyok, de talán nem mondom el nekik "játékomnak" nevezzük.
Ya, tapi mungkin jangan memberi tahu mereka kami menyebutnya "mainanku".
Lo sono, magari non dirglielo che lo chiamiamo "il mio giocattolo".
そうさ、でも彼はそうは言わない、 彼らはそれを「”私達の”おもちゃ」と呼ぶんだ。
그렇긴 한데, 장난감이라고 부르는 거 들키면 곤란해.
Jestem, ale może im nie powiem, że nazywamy to "moją zabawką".
Sunt, dar poate nu le spuneți o numim "jucăria mea".
Да, но, может быть, не говорите им что мы называем это "моя игрушка".
แต่ฉัน อาจจะไม่บอกพวกกับเขาเราเรียกมันว่า "ของเล่นของฉัน"
Öyleyim ama belki onlara söyleme biz buna "oyuncağım" diyoruz.
- I am, but maybe don't tell anyone
- Ja, aber sag besser keinem,
- Eu estou, mas talvez não diga a ninguém
- Lo estoy, pero quizá no le digas a nadie
you call it my toy, honey
dass du es mein Spielzeug nennst, Schatz,
que você chama ele de meu brinquedo, querida
que le llamas mi juguete, cariño.
Ils nous enverraient la facture à mille milliards.
They may ask us to cover the trillion-dollar bill.
sonst müssen wir noch die Billionen-Dollar Rechnung zahlen.
Ou podem pedir para cobrir a conta de trilhões de dólares.
Puede que nos pidan pagar la cuenta de tres trillones
ربما سيطلبون منا أن ندفع فاتورة التريليون دولار
Podrien demanar-nos que paguem el trilió de dòlars de la factura.
他們可能會問我們 覆蓋萬億美元的賬單。
Mohli by nás požádat k pokrytí bilionových nákladu.
Μπορεί να μας ζητήσουν να πληρώσουμε το λογαριασμό, ένα τρισεκατομμύριο κάνει.
Megkérhetnek minket a trillió dollárost.
Mereka mungkin bertanya kepada kami untuk menutupi tagihan triliun dolar.
Potrebbero chiederci di coprire il conto da un trilione di dollari.
あとで俺にいろいろと聞いてくるだろうな、 何兆ドルもかかってるんだ。
그게 얼마 짜린데, 나보고 돈 내라고 할 지도 모르잖아.
Mogą nas zapytać o pokrycie rachunku na bilion dolarów.
Ne pot întreba pentru a acoperi factura de trilion de dolari.
Они могут спросить нас чтобы покрыть триллион долларов.
พวกเขาอาจขอให้เราครอบคลุมการเรียกเก็บเงินล้านล้านดอลลาร์
Bize sorabilirler trilyon dolarlık banknotu kapatmak için.
de dólares.
هي
Ei.
嘿。
Ahoj.
Ε.
Hé.
Hei.
Hey.
なあ。
여보.
Hej.
Hei.
Привет.
เฮ้
Hey.
Ei.
Look at me.
Sieh mich an.
Olhe para mim.
Mírame.
Je reviendrai.
سأعود
Tornaré.
我要回來了。
Vrátím se.
Θα επιστρέψω.
Visszajövök.
Aku kembali.
Tornerò.
俺は帰ってくる。
난 돌아올 거야.
Wrócę.
Revin.
Я возвращаюсь.
ผมจะกลับมา
Geri geliyorum.
I'm coming back.
Ich komme zurück.
Estou voltando.
Volveré.
I always do.
Das tue ich immer.
Eu sempre volto.
Siempre lo hago.
Comme à chaque fois.
دائما أقوم بذلك
Sempre ho faig.
我一直這樣做。
Vždycky jsem to udělal.
Πάντα επιστρέφω.
Mindig is.
Aku selalu melakukannya.
L'ho sempre fatto.
俺がいつもしているように。
항상 그랬고
Zawsze wracam.
Întotdeauna am făcut-o.
Я всегда так делал.
ผมจะทำมัน
Her zaman yaptım.
Je m'y risquerais pas sinon.
لن أقوم بهذا إن لم أعتقد ذلك
No ho faria si pensés el contrari.
我不會這樣做 如果我不這麼認為
Neudělal bych to pokud si myslím jinak.
Δεν θα το έκανα αν αμφέβαλλα έστω για μια στιγμή.
Ezt nem tenném ha másképp gondolnám.
Aku tidak akan melakukan ini jika saya berpikir sebaliknya.
Non lo farei se pensassi diversamente.
浮気なんてしてたら、こんなことは言わない。
못 돌아올 것 같았으면 하려고도 안 했지.
Nie zrobiłbym tego gdybym myślał inaczej.
Nu aș face asta dacă aș crede altceva.
Я бы этого не делал если бы я думал иначе.
ผมจะไม่ทำแบบนี้หากผมคิดเป็นอย่างอื่น
Bunu yapmam Aksi takdirde düşündüm.
I wouldn't do this if I thought otherwise.
Wenn ich das nicht denken würde, würde ich nicht gehen.
Eu não faria isso se pensasse diferente.
No haría esto si pensara lo contrario.
T'as intérêt...
حريّ بك ذلك.
Val més que ho facis...
你更好......
Radši ...
Κανόνισε...
Jobban tennéd...
Kamu lebih baik...
È meglio...
もちろんよ…
Ty lepiej...
Tu mai bine...
Ты лучше...
คุณดีกว่า...
Daha iyisin...
꼭...
- You better.
- Besser ist das.
- Acho bom.
- Mas te vale.
Tu te débarrasseras pas de moi aussi facilement.
나랑 그렇게 쉽게 헤어질 수 있을 줄 알았어?
لا يمكنكِ التخلص مني بهذه السهولة
No podràs desfer-te de mi tan fàcilment.
你不能輕易擺脫我。
Nemůžeš se mě zbavit tak snadno.
Δε θα με ξεφορτωθείς τόσο εύκολα.
Nem tudod könnyen megszabadulni tőlem.
Kamu tidak dapat menyingkirkanku dengan mudah.
Non puoi liberarti di me così facilmente.
俺は簡単には離れない。
Nie możesz tak łatwo się mnie pozbyć.
Nu poți scăpa de mine atât de ușor.
Вы не можете избавиться от меня так легко.
คุณจะไม่ทิ้งผมไปก่อนน่ะ
Benden bu kadar kolay kurtulamazsın.
- You can't get rid of me that easy.
- So schnell wirst du mich nicht los.
- Você não vai se livrar de mim tão fácil.
- No te puedes deshacer de mi tan fácilmente.
(melancholy music)
(engine humming)
Contrôle, les voyants sont au vert. Confirmez.
مركز القيادة نحن على أتم الاستعداد وننتظر التأكيد
Control, els sensors són a punt. Si-us-plau, confirmeu.
飛行，我們全面綠色。 請確認。
Let, máme zelenou. Prosím potvrďte.
Κέντρο έχουμε πράσινο φώς. Επιβεβαιώστε.
Repülés, zöldek vagyunk az egész fórumon. Kérem erősítse meg.
Penerbangan kami berwarna hijau di seluruh papan. Mohon konfirmasi.
Volo, siamo verdi su tutta la linea. Per favore confermare.
こちらは全てグリーン。 確認してださい。
Kontrola, wszystkie wskaźniki zielone. Proszę potwierdź.
Zbor, suntem verzi peste tot. Vă rugăm să confirmați.
Полет, все зеленое по всем направлениям. Пожалуйста подтвердите.
เที่ยวบินที่เรามีสีเขียวทั่วกระดาน กรุณากดยืนยัน
Uçuş, tahta boyunca yeşiliz. Lütfen onaylayın.
플라이트, 전부 양호하다. 확인 바람.
Flight, we are green across the board, please confirm.
Flight, alles grün, warte auf Bestätigung.
Vôo, estamos prontos em toda a linha, por favor confirme.
Vuelo, estamos en verde, por favor confirma.
- [Sarah] Confirmed, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Bestätigt, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Confirmado, Longshot.
Confirmé, Longshot.
تم التأكيد "لونج شوت"
Confirmat, Longshot.
確認，遠射。
Potvrzeno, Longshot.
Επιβεβαιώνουμε Longshot.
Megerősítve, Longshot.
Dikonfirmasi, sedikit kemungkinannya.
Confermato, Longshot.
確認した、ロングショット。
확인했네, 롱샷.
Potwierdzam, Longshot.
Confirmat, Longshot.
Подтверждено, Longshot.
ยืนยันแล้ว, Longshot
Onaylandı, Longshot.
Déverrouillage.
فصل الأقفال
Desacoblant els enclavaments.
脫離聯​​鎖。
Odpojení blokování.
Απασφαλίζω.
A reteszek kikapcsolása.
Melepaskan kaitan.
Blocchi disinnestati.
インターロック解除
연결부 분리
Odłączanie zaczepów.
Deblocarea blocurilor.
Отключение блокировок.
ปลดล็อคอินเตอร์ล็อค
Ayrılma kilitleri.
- Disengaging interlocks.
- Interlocks werden eingestellt.
- Desengatando intertravamentos.
- Desenganchando los candados interiores.
Contrôle, paré pour passage FTL.
مركز القيادة، جاهزون للتشغيل الأسرع من الضوء
Vol, preparat per iniciar la propulsió.
飛行，我們是FTL刻錄。
Let, jdeme na vypalování FTL.
Κέντρο, ξεκινάμε υπερταχύτητα.
Repülés, mi vagyunk az FTL égetésére.
Penerbangan, kami harus membakar FTL.
Volo, siamo pronti per la masterizzazione FTL.
我々は超光速航行をしようとしている。
플라이트, FTL 시동 준비 완료.
Kontrola, jestem gotowy na odpalenie FTL.
Zbor, suntem un du-te pentru FTL arde.
Полет, мы идем к запуску FTL.
เที่ยวบินพวกเราไปเพื่อทดสอบระบบ FTL
Uçuş, FTL yanmasına gidiyoruz.
Flight, we are a go for FTL burn.
Flight, wir sind bereit für FTL-Antrieb.
Vôo, estamos prontos para queimar o FTL.
Vuelo, estamos listos para la quema de FTL.
C'est maintenant ou jamais.
إنه الآن أو أبداً
És ara o mai.
機不可失，勿失良機。
Teď nebo nikdy.
Ή τώρα ή ποτέ.
Most vagy soha.
Sekarang atau tidak pernah.
È ora o mai più.
そしてそのチャンスは今しかない。
신호만 주면 가겠다.
Teraz albo nigdy.
E acum ori niciodată.
Сейчас или никогда.
มันเริ่มตอนนี้ใช่มั้ย
Ya şimdi ya da asla.
It's now or never.
Jetzt oder nie.
É agora ou nunca.
Es ahora o nunca.
- [Sarah] God speed, Commander.
- [Sarah] Gute Reise, Commander.
- [Sarah] Na velocidade de Deus, Comandante.
- [Sarah] Buena suerte, Comandante.
Bonne chance, commandant.
رحلة موفقة أيها القائد
Déu vos guard, comandant.
神速，指揮官。
Božská rychlost, veliteli.
Καλά γκάζια κυβερνήτη.
Isten sebessége, parancsnok.
Sukses, Komandan.
Buona velocità comandante.
ゴッドスピード船長。
행운을 비네, 함장.
Niech Bóg będzie z Tobą komandorze.
Dumnezeu viteză, comandant.
Бог скорости, командир.
ความเร็วของพระเจ้า ผู้บัญชาการ
Tanrı hızı, Komutan.
On se revoit de l'autre côté.
نراك في الجانب الآخر
Us veuré a l'altre banda.
在另一邊見。
Uvidíme se na druhé straně.
Τα λέμε στην άλλη άκρη.
Találkozunk a másik oldalon.
Sampai jumpa di sisi lain.
Ci vediamo dall'altra parte.
反対側で会いましょう。
목적지에서 다시 만나지.
Do zobaczenia po drugiej stronie.
Ne vedem pe cealaltă parte.
Увидимся на другой стороне.
แล้วพบกันในอีกด้านหนึ่งน่ะ
Diğer tarafta görüşürüz.
See you on the other side.
Wir sehen uns auf der anderen Seite.
Vejo você do outro lado,
Nos vemos en el otro lado.
Allez, Contrôle. J'attends. Vous pouvez le faire.
هيا مركز القيادة لأسمعها، يمكنكِ القيام بذلك
Vinga, Control. Que així sigui, ho podeu fer.
來吧，飛行。 讓我們聽聽，你可以做到。
Pojď, Flight. Slyšíme to, můžete to udělat.
Ελα κέντρο. Πές το, μπορείς.
Gyerünk, Repülés. Halljuk meg, meg tudod csinálni.
Ayo, Penerbangan. Mari kita dengarkan, Kau bisa melakukannya.
さあ、フライトだ。 またすぐ交信することにしよう。
어서요, 플라이트. 그렇게 자신이 없습니까?
Daj spokój. Posłuchaj tego: dasz radę.
Haide, Zborul. Să-l auzim, o puteți face.
Давай, полет. Давайте послушаем, вы можете сделать это.
มาเลยเที่ยวบิน มาฟังกันเลย คุณทำได้
Hadi Uçuş. Bunu duyalım, yapabilirsin.
Dai, Volo. Sentiamo, puoi farlo.
- Come on Flight, let's hear it, you can do it.
- Komm schon Flight, ich will es hören, Sie können das.
- Vamos lá vôo, vamos ouvir, você pode fazer isso.
- Vamos Vuelo, vamos a escucharlo, puedes hacerlo.
- Fine.
- Na gut.
- Tranquilo.
- Bueno.
D'accord.
Bene.
حسناً
Bé.
精細。
Dobře.
Καλά.
Bírság.
Baik.
いいですね。
좋아.
W porządku.
Amenda.
Хорошо.
ละเอียด
İnce.
Ainsi soit-il, commandant.
Make it so, Commander.
Machen Sie es so, Commander.
Faça acontecer, comandante.
Hazlo así, Comandante.
"قم بعمله" أيها القائد
Faci-ho, comandant.
這麼做，指揮官。
Udělejte to, veliteli.
"Καλή επιτυχία", Κυβερνήτη.
Tedd meg, parancsnok.
Jadikan begitu, Komandan.
そうしましょう、船長。
증명해 봐, 함장.
Zrób to, komandorze
Fă-o așa, Comandante.
Сделай так, коммандер.
ทำมันให้ได้ ผู้บัญชาการ
Öyle yap, Komutan.
Fallo così, comandante.
Voilà.
- [Ethan] There you go.
- [Ethan] Na bitte.
- [Ethan] Lá vai você.
- [Ethan] Ahí lo tienen.
ها أنتِ هنا
Som-hi.
你去吧
Tady máš.
Αυτή είσαι.
Nesze.
Ini dia.
Ecco qua.
現在移動中。
그렇게 나와야지.
Proszę bardzo.
Acolo te duci.
Вот и ты.
ไปล่ะ
İşte gidiyorsun.
- [Reporter] The world awaits the test
- [Reporter] Die Welt wartet auf den Test des ersten
- [Reporter] O mundo aguarda o teste
- [Sarah] El mundo espera la prueba
of the very first faster-than-light propulsion system.
Antriebsystems, das schneller als Lichtgeschwindigkeit ist.
do primeiro sistema de propulsão mais rápido que a luz.
del primer sistema de propulsión mas rápido que la luz.
... du premier moteur à dépasser la vitesse de la lumière.
... بواسطة أول نظام دفع أسرع من الضوء.
... del primer sistema de propulsió Més Ràpid que la Llum (MRL).
...比光快的第一個 推進系統。
... z prvního rychlejšího než světla pohonný systém.
... για πρώτη φορά ένα σύστημα πρόωσης γρηγορότερο απ' το φως.
... az első gyorsabb, mint a fény Propulziós rendszer.
... yang pertama lebih cepat dari cahaya sistem propulsi.
... del primissimo più veloce della luce sistema di propulsione.
世界初となる超高速推進システムを搭載していて
...최초의 초광속 추친 시스템을 탑재하고 있습니다.
... pierwszy z szybszych niż światło układ napędowy.
... de la primul mai rapid decât lumina sistem de propulsie.
... самая первая сверхсветовая двигательная установка.
... แห่งแรกที่เร็วกว่าระบบขับเคลื่อนด้วยแสง
... ilk ışıktan daha hızlı tahrik sistemi.
The Longshot is the most advanced spacecraft ever built.
Die Longshot ist das modernste Raumschiff aller Zeiten.
O Longshot é a espaçonave mais avançada já construída.
El Longshot es la nave mas avanzada jamás creada.
Le Longshot est le vaisseau le plus sophistiqué jamais construit.
"لونج شوت" هي أكثر مركبة فضاء تقدماً تم صنعها.
La Longshot és la nau espacial més avançada mai construïda,
Longshot是最多的 先進的太空飛船。
Longshot je nejvíc pokročilé vesmírné plavidlo, které kdy bylo postaveno
Το Longshot είναι το πιό προηγμένο διαστημόπλοιο που έχει κατασκευαστεί ποτέ.
A Longshot a leginkább a valaha épített fejlett űrhajók.
Kesimpulannya adalah pesawat ruang angkasa paling canggih yang pernah dibangun.
Il Longshot è il più space craft avanzato mai costruito.
この”ロングショット号”が これまでに造られた中で最も高度な宇宙船となります。
롱샷은 역사상 가장 진보한 우주선이라고 할 수 있죠.
Longshot jest najbardziej zaawansowanym pojazdem kosmicznym jaki kiedykolwiek zbudowano.
Longshot-ul este cel mai mult ambarcațiuni avansate construite vreodată.
Longshot является самым продвинутым космическим кораблем, из когда-либо построенных
Longshot เป็นยานอวกาศที่ทันสมัยที่สุดเท่าที่เคยสร้างมา
Longshot en çok gelişmiş uzay aracı şimdiye kadar üretildi.
And in it, Commander Kane will travel to Mars.
Und darin wird Commander Kane zum Mars reisen.
E nele, o comandante Kane viajará até Marte.
Y en ella, el Comandante Kane viajará a Marte.
À l'intérieur, le commandant Kane ira jusqu'à Mars.
وفيها، القائد كين سيسافر إلى المريخ.
i amb ella, el comandant Kane viatjarà a Mart.
在其中，凱恩指揮官 將前往火星。
A v tom, velitel Kane bude cestovat na Mars.
Και μ' αυτό ο Κυβερνήτης Κέιν θα ταξιδέψει στον Άρη.
És benne, Kane parancsnok Marsba utazik.
Dan di dalamnya, Komandan Kane akan melakukan perjalanan ke Mars.
E dentro, comandante Kane viaggerà su Marte.
そして、そのケイン船長が 火星を旅行することになります。
그리고 그 우주선으로 케인 지휘관이 화성으로 향하게 됩니다.
A w nim komandor Kane będzie podróżować na Marsa.
Și în asta, comandant Kane va călători pe Marte.
И в этом, командующий Кейн поедет на Марс.
และในนั้น Commander ลุงตู่ จะเดินทางไปดาวอังคาร
Ve içinde, Komutan Kane Mars'a seyahat edecek.
A journey that, according to NASA,
Eine Reise, die laut NASA
Uma jornada que, de acordo com a NASA,
Una travesía que, de acuerdo con la NASA,
Un voyage qui, selon la NASA, prendra trois minutes.
الرحلة كما تقول ناسا ستستغرق أكثر بقليل من ٣ دقائق
Un viatge que, segons la NASA, s'allargarà poc més de tres minuts.
根據美國國家航空航天局的說法， 將需要超過三分鐘。
Cesta, která podle NASA, bude trvat něco přes tři minuty.
Ένα ταξίδι που σύμφωνα με την NASA, θα διαρκέσει λίγο πάνω από τρία λεπτά.
Egy út, amely a NASA szerint csak három percet vesz igénybe.
Sebuah perjalanan yang, menurut NASA, akan memakan waktu lebih dari tiga menit.
Un viaggio che, secondo la NASA, ci vorranno poco più di tre minuti.
NASAによると、今回の旅は 3分程度かかります。
그리고 이 여정은 NASA에 의하면, 3분 정도밖에 걸리지 않을 것이라고 합니다.
Podróż, według NASA zajmie nieco ponad trzy minuty.
O călătorie care, potrivit NASA, va dura puțin peste trei minute.
Путешествие, которое, согласно НАСА, займет чуть более трех минут.
การเดินทางที่นาซ่าอ้างอิงจะใช้เวลาเพียงสามนาที
NASA'ya göre bir yolculuk, sadece üç dakikadan fazla sürecek.
will take just over three minutes.
etwas mehr als drei Minuten dauern wird.
levará apenas três minutos.
solo tomará poco mas de tres minutos.
- [Ethan] Lighting it up
- [Ethan] Start in drei, zwei eins.
- [Ethan] Acendendo
- [Ethan] Encendiéndolo
Allumage dans trois,
التشغيل في ثلاثة
Encenent en tres,
將它點亮三個，
Světlo za tři,
Πυροδότηση σε τρία
Megvilágítva háromszor,
Menyalakannya dalam tiga,
Accendendola in tre,
機関始動、３…
시동까지 3,
Odpalam na trzy,
Luminându-l în trei,
Зажигая в три,
แสงสว่างขึ้นใน 3
Üçte aydınlatmak,
in three, two, one. (engine whining)
em três, dois, um.
en tres, dos, uno.
deux, un...
إثنان، واحد...
dos, un ...
二，一......
dva, jeden ...
δύο, ένα...
kettő, egy ...
dua, satu ...
due uno...
2…1…
2, 1...
dwa, jeden...
doi unu...
два один...
2 1
iki bir...
Allumage !
تعليم!
Ara!
標記！
Označit!
Τώρα!
Mark!
Menandai!
Marchio!
マーク！
시동!
Teraz
Marcă!
Отметка!
เป้าหมาย!
İşaret!
Mark!
Los!
¡Mark!
(people chattering)
(ethereal music)
(energy crackling)
(spaceship rumbling)
(tense music)
1,25 c.
١.٢٥ سي "سي c هو ثابت سرعة الضوء"
1.25 c。
1,25 c.
1.25 c
現在光速の1.25倍
1.25C
1,25 prędkości światła
1,25 c.
1,25 с.
1.25 c.
1,25 c.
Ralentissement dans cinq secondes.
تخفيض الدوران في خمسة.
Desaccelerant d'aquí cinc segons.
旋轉五下。
Přetočení do pěti.
Επιβράδυνση σε πέντε.
Ötben lefelé forgatva.
Berputar dalam lima.
Rotolando giù in cinque.
スピンダウンまで5秒
회전 감속까지 5초
Se rotește în cinci.
Спиннинг в пять.
ปั่นลงใน 5
Beş dakikada dönüyor.
Wychodzę za 5 (sekund)
Spinning down in five.
Runterfahren in fünf.
Girando em cinco.
Bajando a cinco.
(spaceship whooshing) (engine whining)
HAUTE ORBITE DE MARS
Mars - wysoka orbita
Órbita Alta de Marte
hohe Umlaufbahn des Mars
Flight, do you copy?
Flight, sind Sie da?
Vôo, você copia?
Vuelo, ¿me copias?
Contrôle, vous me recevez ?
مركز القيادة، هل يمكنك التأكيد؟
Control, em sentiu?
飛行，你複製？
Let, kopíruješ?
Κέντρο, λαμβάνεις ;
Repül, másolsz?
Penerbangan, apakah kau menyalin?
Volo, copi?
フライト、コンプリート。
플라이트, 들립니까?
Zbor, copiezi?
Рейс, ты копируешь?
เที่ยวบินคุณคัดลอกแล้ว?
Uçuş, duyuyor musun?
Kontrola, słyszycie mnie?
(Mission Control applauding) - That's right, yes!
Genau, ja!
Isso aí!
- ¡Eso es, sí!
Cinq sur cinq, commandant.
بكل وضوح أيها القائد.
Alt i clar, comandant.
指揮官，響亮而清晰。
Hlasitý a jasný, veliteli.
Δυνατά και καθαρά, Κυβερνήτη.
Hangos és világos, parancsnok.
Keras dan jelas, Komandan.
Forte e chiaro, comandante.
大声ではっきり聞こえるわ、船長。
아주 잘 들리네, 함장.
Głośno i wyraźnie, komandorze.
Tare și clar, comandant.
Громко и ясно, командующий.
ดังและชัดเจน ลุงตู่
Yüksek sesle ve net, Komutan.
- Loud and clear, Commander.
- Wir hören Sie klar und deutlich, Commander.
- Alto e claro, comandante.
- Fuerte y claro, Comandante.
Welcome back to our corner of space-time.
Willkommen zurück in unserer Ecke von Raum und Zeit.
Bem-vindo de volta ao nosso canto do espaço-tempo.
Bienvenido de vuelta a nuestro rincón del espacio-tiempo.
Vous êtes de retour dans notre espace-temps.
مرحباً بعودتك إلى زاويتنا في الزمكان.
Benvingut de nou al nostre racó de l'espaitemps.
歡迎回來 到了我們時空的角落。
Vítej zpět do našeho rohu vesmírného času.
Καλωσήρθες πίσω στη δική μας γωνιά του χωροχρόνου.
Üdv újra a téridő idejére.
Selamat datang kembali ke sudut waktu ruang kita.
Ben tornato al nostro angolo di spazio.
お帰りなさい 私達と同じ速さの宇宙に。
이쪽 우주 시간으로 돌아온 것을 환영하네.
Witamy znowu w naszym zakątku czasoprzestrzeni.
Bine ai revenit în colțul nostru de timp spațial.
Добро пожаловать в наш угол пространства-времени.
ยินดีต้อนรับกลับสู่มุมเวลาว่างของเรา
Tekrar hoşgeldiniz uzay zamanımızın köşesine.
Heureux d'être de retour.
حسناً، من الجيد أن نعود.
Està bé tornar a ser-hi.
嗯，回來真好。
No, to je dobré být zpátky.
Λοιπόν, είναι ωραία να επιστρέφεις.
Nos, ez jó, hogy visszajöjjön.
Yah, senang bisa kembali.
Bene, è bello essere tornati.
戻ってこれてうれしいよ。
뭐, 돌아와서 좋네요 저도.
No cóż, dobrze jest wrócić.
E bine să te întorci.
Ну, это хорошо, чтобы вернуться.
ดีที่ได้กลับมา
Şey, geri dönmek güzel.
- [Ethan] It's good to be back.
- [Ethan] Schön wieder da zu sein.
- [Ethan] É bom estar de volta.
- [Ethan] Es bueno estar de regreso.
- And this just in!
- Wir haben gerade gehört,
- E isso em apenas!
- ¡Y esto acaba de llegar!
Ça vient d'arriver !
وهذا وصلنا للتو!
I ho acaba d'aconseguir!
而這只是在！
A právě to!
Και αυτό ήταν !
És ez csak!
Dan ini baru saja masuk!
E questo solo!
速報です。
그리고 마침내
I po prostu jest!
Și asta doar!
И это только в!
และนี่เพิ่งเข้ามา
Ve bu sadece içinde!
Commander Kane has arrived at his destination
dass Commander Kane an seinem Zielort angekommen ist
Comandante Kane chegou ao seu destino
El comandante Kane ha llegado a su destino
Le commandant Kane est arrivé à sa destination
القائد كين قد وصل إلى وُجهته.
El Comandant Kane ha arribat al seu destí
凱恩司令 已到達目的地
Velitel Kane dorazil na místo určení
Ο Κυβερνήτης Κέιν έφτασε στον προορισμό του.
Kane parancsnok megérkezett a rendeltetési helyre
Komandan Kane telah tiba di tujuannya
Comandante Kane è arrivato a destinazione
ケイン船長が今 目的地に到着しました。
케인 함장이 목표 지점에 도착했습니다.
Komandor Kane dotarł do miejsca przeznaczenia.
Comandantul Kane a ajuns la destinația sa
Командующий Кейн прибыл в пункт назначения
ผู้บัญชาการ ตู่ ไปถึงที่ปลายทางของท่านแล้ว
Komutan Kane hedefine ulaştı
and is now the first man to travel faster than light.
und nun der erste Mann ist, der schneller als Licht reiste.
e agora é o primeiro homem a viajar mais rápido que a luz.
y es ahora el primer hombre en viajar mas rápido que la luz.
et est à présent le premier homme à voyager plus vite que la lumière.
وهو الآن أول رجل
i s'ha convertit en el primer home
現在是第一個男人
a je nyní prvním mužem
και είναι ο πρώτος άνθρωπος
és most az első ember
dan sekarang menjadi manusia pertama
ed è ora il primo uomo
そして今、
빛보다 빠른 속도로 여행한
i jest teraz pierwszym człowiekiem...
și este acum primul om
и теперь первый мужчина
และตอนนี้เขาเป็นนายกคนแรก
ve şimdi ilk insan
يسافر بسرعة أكبر من الضوء
en viatjar més ràpid que la llum.
旅行比光更快。
co cestoval rychleji než světlo.
που ταξίδεψε γρηγορότερα από το φως
gyorsabban utazzon, mint a fény.
untuk melakukan perjalanan lebih cepat dari cahaya.
viaggiare più veloce della luce.
彼は光よりも早い旅行をした最初の男になりました。
최초의 인간이 된 셈이죠.
... który podróżował szybciej niż światło.
pentru a călători mai repede decât lumina.
путешествовал быстрее, чем свет.
ที่เดินทางเร็วกว่าแสง
ışıktan daha hızlı seyahat etmek.
- Thank God!
- Gott sei Dank!
- Graças a Deus!
- ¡Gracias a Dios!
Dieu, merci !
شكراً إلهي!
Gràcies a Déu!
感謝上帝！
Díky bohu!
Δόξα τω Θεώ !
Hála Istennek!
Terima kasih Tuhan!
Grazie Dio!
ああ、助かった！
오 신이시여.
Dzięki Bogu!
Slava Domnului!
Слава Богу!
ขอบคุณพระเจ้า!
Tanrıya şükür!
- [Reporter] The commander will now launch
- [Reporter] Der Commander wird nun
- [Repórter] O comandante vai agora lançar
- [reportera] El comandante ahora lanzará
Le commandant va déployer un satellite quantique
سيطلق القائد الآن قمر صناعي متشابك "قمر متشابك: يعتمد على التشابك الكمّي للاتصالات"
Ara el Comandant llançarà un satèl·lit d'enllaç
指揮官現在將發射 一個糾纏的衛星
Velitel se nyní vypustí uložený satelit
Ο κυβερνήτης θα εκτοξεύσει τώρα ένα συζευγμένο δορυφόρο
A parancsnok most elindul összekapcsolt műhold
Komandan sekarang akan diluncurkan satelit terjerat
Il comandante ora verrà lanciato un satellite aggrovigliato
船長は今量子通信衛星を放出しました。
지금부터 탑재된 위성을 화성 궤도로 사출할텐데요,
Komandor wypuści na orbitę Mars tzw. splątanego satelitę
Comandantul va lansa acum un satelit încurcat
Командир теперь запустит квантовый путник
นายกตู่จะเปิดตัวดาวเทียมติดๆกัน
Komutan şimdi başlayacak dolaşmış bir uydu
an entangled satellite into orbit around Mars
einen Satelliten in die Mars-Umlaufbahn schicken,
um satélite entrelaçado em órbita ao redor de Marte
un satélite entrelazado en órbita al rededor de Marte
en orbite martienne afin de permettre une communication en temps réel
في مدار حول المريخ ليتيح الاتصالات في الزمن الحقيقي "قمر متشابك: يعتمد على التشابك الكمّي للاتصالات"
en òrbita al voltant de Mart que permetrà la comunicació en temps real
進入火星軌道 允許實時通信
na oběžnou dráhu kolem Marsu umožňující komunikaci v reálném čase
σε τροχιά γύρω από τον Άρη επιτρέποντας την επικοινωνία σε πραγματικό χρόνο
a Mars körüli pályára lehetővé teszi a valós idejű kommunikációt
ke orbit putaran Mars memungkinkan komunikasi waktu nyata
in orbita attorno a Marte consentendo la comunicazione in tempo reale
これは火星を周回し、時差のないリアルタイム通信を。
위성은 지구와, 화성 1호 식민지 사이에서
który umożliwi komunikację w czasie rzeczywistym...
în orbită pe Marte permițând comunicarea în timp real
на орбиту вокруг Марса позволяет общаться в режиме реального времени
เข้าสู่วงโคจรรอบดาวอังคารช่วยให้สามารถสื่อสารแบบเรียลไทม์ได้
Mars'ın yörüngesine girdi gerçek zamanlı iletişime izin vermek
allowing real-time communication
wodurch Echtzeit-Kommunikation
permitindo comunicação em tempo real
permitiendo la comunicación en tiempo real
between Earth and Mars Colony One.
zwischen der Erde und Mars Kolonie Eins möglich wird.
entre a Terra e a Colônia Marte Um.
entre la Tierra y la Colonia Uno de Marte.
entre la Terre et la colonie martienne.
بين الأرض ومستعمرة المريخ الأولى "قمر متشابك: يعتمد على التشابك الكمّي للاتصالات"
entre la Terra i la Colònia One de Mart.
地球和火星之間的殖民地之一。
mezi Zemí a Mars Colony One.
μεταξύ της Γης και της Αποικίας του Άρη.
a Föld és a Mars Colony One között.
antara Bumi dan Mars Koloni Satu.
tra la Terra e Marte Colony One.
地球と火星コロニーワンの間に確立します。
실시간 통신이 이루어지도록 해 줄 겁니다.
.. między Ziemią a Mars Colony 1.
între Pământ și Colonia Unu.
между Землей и Марсом Колония Один.
ระหว่าง Earth กับ Mars Colony One
Dünya ile Mars Kolonisi Biri arasında.
(dramatic music)
Q sat, en ligne.
القمر الكُمّي، يعمل
Satèl·lit Q, en línia.
Q坐在網上。
Q satelit, online.
Δορυφόρος Q, σε απευθείας σύνδεση.
Q online, online.
Q sat, online.
Q seduto, online.
量子衛生オンライン。
Q 위성, 작동 확인.
Q sat, online.
Q sat, on-line.
Q сел, онлайн.
ดาวเทียมของช่อง One 31 ออนไลน์
Q çevrimiçi oturdu.
- Q sat, online.
- Q Sat, Online.
- Satélite q, en línea.
Bien.
- [Ethan] All right, let's do this again
- [Ethan] Okay, machen wir das noch einmal,
- [Ethan] Tudo bem, vamos fazer isso de novo
- [Ethan] Muy bien, hagámoslo de nuevo
حسناً
Perfecte.
行。
Dobře.
Εντάξει.
Rendben.
Baiklah.
Tutto ok.
よし。
좋아.
W porządku.
In regula.
Отлично.
เอาล่ะ
Tamam.
Remettons ça, avant que je vous manque trop.
لنقم بعمل ذلك مرة أخرى قبل أن تفقدوني كثيراً
Tornem-ho a fer, abans no em trobeu massa a faltar.
我們再來一次 在你太想念我之前。
Uděláme to znovu, než se mi budete moc chybět.
Ας το ξανακάνουμε, πριν σας ξεφύγω πάρα πολύ.
Tegyük meg ezt újra, mielőtt túl sokat hiányozol.
Ayo lakukan ini lagi, sebelum kamu terlalu merindukanku.
Facciamolo di nuovo, prima che tu mi manchi troppo.
あなたが私を恋しく思う前に。 もう一度やりましょう。
날 너무 그러워하게 되기 전에 돌아가야겠는걸.
Zróbmy to jeszcze raz, zanim za mną za bardzo zatęsknicie.
Să facem asta din nou, înainte să îmi lipsești prea mult.
Давайте сделаем это снова, прежде чем скучать по мне слишком сильно.
ลองทำอีกครั้งก่อนที่จะคิดถึงผมมากเกินไป
Bunu tekrar yapalım. beni çok özlemeden önce
before you miss me too much.
bevor ihr mich zu sehr vermisst.
antes de você sentir muita falta de mim.
antes de que me extrañes mucho.
Initialisez la séquence de retour.
ابدأ إجراءات العودة
Inicieu la seqüència de retorn.
啟動返回序列。
Spusťte postup zpět.
Ξεκινήστε τη διαδικασία επιστροφής.
A visszatérési sorrend indítása.
Lakukan urutan pengembalian.
Iniziare la sequenza di restituzione.
リターンシーケンスを開始します。
귀환 단계에 돌입하게
Rozpocznij sekwencję powrotną.
Inițiați secvența de retur.
Инициировать последовательность возврата.
เริ่มต้นลำดับการส่งคืน
Dönüş sırasını başlat.
- Initiate return sequence.
- Rückflugs-Sequenz starten.
- Inicie a sequência de retorno.
- Inicien la secuencia de regreso.
- [Ethan] Starting FTL spin-up sequence.
- [Ethan] Starte FTL Rückflug-Sequenz.
- [Ethan] Iniciando a sequência de aceleração da FTL.
- [Ethan] Comenzando la secuencia de giro de FTL.
Initialisation de la rotation.
البدء بإجراءات التدوير الأسرع من الضوء
Iniciant la seqüència de retorn MRL.
啟動FTL旋轉序列。
Spuštění relační sekvence FTL.
Ξεκινώ την ακολουθία περιστροφής υπερταχύτητας.
FTL spin-up szekvencia indítása.
Mulai urutan spin-up FTL.
Avvio della sequenza di spin-up FTL.
FTLスピンアップシーケンスの開始
FTL 회전 단계 시작
Uruchamianie sekwencji FTL.
Pornirea secvenței de spin-up FTL.
Запуск последовательности раскрутки FTL.
เริ่มต้นลำดับการหมุนวงวาป
FTL döndürme sırasını başlatıyor.
Bien reçu, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Roger that, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Roger, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Confirmado, Longshot.
- [Sarah] Enterada, Longshot.
عُلم ذلك "لونج شوت"
Entesos, Longshot.
羅傑，遠射。
Roger k Longshot.
Ελήφθη, Longshot.
Roger, Longshot.
Roger itu, kemungkinannya.
Roger quello, Longshot.
わかった？、ロングショット。
확인했네, 롱샷.
Roger, Longshot.
Roger asta, Longshot.
Понял, Лонгшот.
Roger ที่ Longshot
Anlaşıldı Longshot.
(spaceship humming)
Voyants au vert, Contrôle.
ونحن جاهزون تماماً مركز القيادة.
Tenim llum verda, Control.
我們走了 飛行。
A my jsme připraveni jít přes palubu,Flight
Και πάμε για την άλλη μεριά, Κέντρο.
És mi megyünk a fedélzeten, Repülés.
Dan kita harus jalan di seluruh papan, Penerbangan.
E noi siamo un go su tutta la linea, volo.
そして私達は行く 全面的に、フライト。
상태 전부 양호하다, 플라이트.
Wygląda na to, że wszystko w porządku na pokładzie.
Și noi suntem un du-te peste bord, zborul.
И мы идем через борт, полет.
และพวกเรากำลังไปทั่วกระดานบิน
Ve biz bir yoldayız tahtanın karşısında, Uçuş.
- And we are a go across the board, Flight.
- Hier ist alles grün, Flight.
- E nós estamos na frente, vôo.
- Y estamos a través del tablero, Vuelo.
- [Sarah] Spin her up, Commander.
- [Sarah] Fliegen Sie los, Commander.
- [Sarah] Gire ela, Comandante.
- [Sarah] Gírala hacia arriba, Comandante.
Allez-y, commandant.
دورها أيها القائد
Endavant, comandant.
指揮官，把她旋轉起來。
Otočte ji, veliteli.
Δώσ' του, Κυβερνήτη.
Spin őt, parancsnok.
Putar, Komandan.
Spinela su, comandante.
スピンアップさせて。
출발하게, 함장.
Rozkręć ją, komandorze.
Rotiți-o, comandant.
Раскрути ее, командир.
หมุนเธอขึ้นมา ผู้บัญชาการ
Döndür onu Komutan.
(engine whining)
Contrôle, j'ai un problème de verrouillage.
مركز القيادة، يبدو أنني أواجه مشكلة في القفل التشابكي
Control, sembla que hi ha un problema als enclavaments.
飛行，看起來我可能有 這裡是一個互鎖問題。
Flight, vypadá to, že bych mohl mít problém interlocku zde.
Κέντρο, μάλλον έχω ένα θέμα απασφάλισης εδώ.
Repülés, úgy tűnik, hogy lehet itt egy interlock-probléma.
Penerbangan, sepertinya aku punya masalah interlock di sini.
Volo, sembra che possa avere un problema di interlock qui.
フライト、インターロックの問題が発生しているようです。
플라이트, 연결부에 문제가 좀 생긴 것 같은데.
Kontrola, wygląda na to, że mogę mieć usterkę zaczepów.
Zborul, se pare că am putea o problemă de interblocare aici.
Центр, похоже, у меня может здесь быть проблема блокировки .
เที่ยวบิน ดูเหมือนว่าผมอาจมีปัญหาเรื่องอินเตอร์ล็อคที่นี่
Uçuş, benimki gibi gözüküyor Burada bir kilitleme sorunu.
- Flight, it looks like I may have an interlock issue here.
- Flight, ich scheine ein Interlock-Problem zu haben.
- Vôo, parece que eu tenho um bloqueio aqui.
- Vuelo, parece que quizá tenga un
problema de entrelazamiento.
Même constat ici.
نرى نفس المشكلة هنا
Estem veient el mateix aquí.
我們在這看到同樣的事情。
Vidíme tu totéž.
Το ίδιο βλέπουμε κι εμείς εδώ.
Ugyanezt látjuk itt.
Kami melihat hal yang sama di sini.
Stiamo vedendo la stessa cosa qui.
ここでも同じことが見られるわ。
우리 쪽에서도 확인되고 있네.
Widzimy to samo tutaj.
Vedem același lucru aici.
Мы видим то же самое здесь.
เราเห็นสิ่งเดียวกันที่นี่
Burada da aynı şeyi görüyoruz.
- We're seeing the same thing here.
- Das sehen wir hier auch.
- Estamos vendo a mesma coisa aqui.
- Estamos viendo lo mismo aquí.
Lancez un diagnostic.
Let's take a look at diagnostics.
Schauen wir uns die Diagnostik an.
Vamos dar uma olhada no diagnóstico.
Vamos a revisar los diagnósticos.
لنلق نظرة على التشخيص
Fem un cop d'ull als diagnòstics.
我們來看看診斷。
Podívejme se na diagnostiku.
Ας ρίξουμε μια ματιά στα διαγνωστικά.
Nézzük meg a diagnosztikát.
Mari kita lihat diagnosa.
Diamo un'occhiata alla diagnostica.
診断を見てみましょう。
점검을 한번 해 보지.
Rzućmy okiem na diagnostykę.
Să aruncăm o privire la diagnosticare.
Давайте посмотрим на диагностику.
ลองดูที่การวินิจฉัยสิ
Teşhislere bir göz atalım.
Annulez le saut et coupez la rotation.
قم بإيقاف المحرك الأسرع من الضوء وأوقف الدوران
Aborteu l'inici de la unitat MRL i desaccelereu.
中止FTL驅動器啟動和減速。
Zrušte start spouštění jednotky FTL.
Ακύρωση εκκίνησης της μονάδας υπερταχύτητας και επιβράδυνση.
Az FTL-meghajtó megszakítása és leállítása.
Batalkan FTL drive start dan spin down.
Interrompere l'avvio del convertitore FTL e avviare la rotazione.
FTLドライブの起動を中止してスピンダウンさせて。
FTL 단계를 종료하고 회전을 멈추게.
Przerwij rozruch FTL i spróbuj wyhamować obrót.
Renunțați la declanșarea și deplasarea unității FTL.
Прервите запуск привода FTL и начните вращение.
ยกเลิกระบบวาป มันเริ่มแล้วกำลังหมุนลง
FTL sürücünün çalışmasını durdurun ve döndürün.
Abort FTL drive start and spin down.
FTL-Antrieb abbrechen und runterfahren.
Interrompa o início e a desaceleração do drive FTL.
Aborta el comienzo del impulso FTL y gírala hacia abajo.
Bien reçu.
عُلم ذلك
Entesos.
收到。
Rozumím.
Ελήφθη.
Értettem.
Diterima.
Ricevuto.
了解。
확인.
Przyjąłem.
Recepționat.
Заметано.
Anlaşıldı.
- Roger that.
- Roger.
- Entendido.
- Enterado.
Rotation annulée.
إيقاف الدوران
Desaccelerant.
旋轉下來。
Přetočení.
Επιβράδυνση.
Spinning le.
Berputar.
Roteare.
スピンダウン。
회전 정지.
Zwalniam obroty.
Îndepărtează-te.
Спиннинг вниз.
Aşağı dönüyor.
Spinning down.
Fahre runter.
Girando para baixo.
Girando hacia abajo.
(computer beeping)
Flight, we have a problem.
Flight, wir haben ein Problem.
Vôo, nós temos um problema.
Vuelo, tenemos un problema.
Contrôle, on a un problème...
مركز القيادة، لدينا مشكلة...
Control, tenim un problema...
飛行，我們有問題......
Flight, máme problém ...
Κέντρο, έχουμε πρόβλημα ...
Repülés, problémánk van ...
Penerbangan, kami memiliki masalah ...
Volo, abbiamo un problema ...
フライト、問題発生...
플라이트, 문제가 좀 생ㄱ...
Kontrola, mamy problem ...
Zborul, avem o problemă ...
Рейс, у нас проблема ...
Uçuş, bir sorunumuz var ...
(spaceship whooshing)
COMMUNICATION ROMPUE
(alarm beeping)
(energy crackling) (dramatic music)
Contrôle, j'ai perdu le contrôle du moteur !
مركز القيادة، فقدت التحكم بالمحرك. أكرر، لقد فقدت التحكم بالمحرك
He perdut el control. Repeteixo, he perdut el control.
飛行，我失去了駕駛控制。 重複一遍，我失去了驅動器控制。
Flight, ztratil jsem kontrolu nad řízením. Opakuji, ztratil jsem řízení pohonu.
Πτήση, έχω χάσει τον έλεγχο των κινητήρων. Επαναλαμβάνω, έχω χάσει τον έλεγχο κινητήρων.
Repülés, elvesztettem a vezetést. Ismételje meg, elvesztettem a hajtásvezérlést.
Penerbangan, aku telah kehilangan kendali drive. Ulangi, aku telah kehilangan kendali drive.
Volo, ho perso il controllo della guida. Ripeti, ho perso il controllo del drive.
フライト、ドライブの制御を失いました。 繰り返します、ドライブの制御を失いました。
플라이트, 드라이브 조종이 불가능하다, 반복, 드라이브 조종이 불가능하다.
Kontrola, straciłem panowanie nad napędem. Powtarzam, straciłem kontrolę nad napędem.
Zborul, am pierdut controlul asupra mașinii. Repetă, am pierdut controlul asupra mișcării.
Рейс, я потерял контроль над приводом. Повторите, я потерял контроль над приводом.
Uçuş, sürüş kontrolünü kaybettim. Tekrar ediyorum, sürüş kontrolünü kaybettim.
Flight, I have lost drive control.
Flight, ich habe die Flugkontrolle verloren.
Vôo, perdi o controle da unidade.
Vuelo, he perdido el control de impulso.
Repeat, I have lost drive control.
Ich wiederhole, Flugkontrolle verloren.
Repito, perdi o controle da unidade.
Repito, he perdido el control de impulso.
I have no nav comm and I am approaching light speed.
Ich habe kein Nav Comm und nähere mich Lichtgeschwindigkeit.
Não tenho controle e estou me aproximando
No tengo comunicación de navegación y me acerco a velocidad
Systèmes de navigation HS et j'approche la vitesse de la lumière.
لا أملك التحكم بالتوجه وأقارب سرعة الضوء
No tinc el comandament de navegació i m'estic acostant a la velocitat de la llum.
我沒有導航通訊 我正在接近光速。
Nemám navigaci a blížím se rychlosti světla.
Δεν έχω εργαλεία πλοήγησης, επικοινωνιών και πλησιάζω ταχύτητα φωτός.
Nincs kapcsolataim és közeledek a fénysebességhez.
aku tidak punya comm nav dan saya mendekati kecepatan cahaya.
Non ho nessuna comunicazione nav e mi sto avvicinando alla velocità della luce.
ナビゲーションがありません！ そして船は光速に近付こうとしています！
목적 좌표도 없이 광속에 도달하고 있다.
Siadła nawigacja i komunikator, zbliżam się do prędkości światła.
Nu am nav nav și mă apropii de viteza luminii.
У меня нет навигационной связи и я приближаюсь к скорости света.
Denizyolu iletişimim yok ve ışık hızına yaklaşıyorum.
da velocidade da luz.
de la luz.
Trouvez-le-moi !
الاتصالات، ابحث عنه!
Trobeu-lo!
找到他，通訊！
Najděte ho, Comms!
Επικοινωνίες, βρείτε τον !
Találd meg, Comms!
Temukan dia, Comms!
Trovalo, Comms!
コムズ！彼を見つけて！
좌표 추적해, 어서!
Znajdź go. Odzyskaj komunikację!
Găsește-l, comuni!
Найди его, Коммс!
Bul onu Comms!
- Find him, Comms!
- Findet ihn, Comms!
- Encontre ele, Comms!
- ¡Encuéntrenlo, Comunicaciones!
Changement de vecteur !
يتم سحبي إلى متجه جديد!
Estic sent arrossegat cap a un nou vector!
我被拉進來 到一個新的載體！
Jsem vtažen do nového vektoru!
Κάτι με τραβάει εκτός πορείας σε νέα κατεύθυνση !
Behúzzam egy új vektorhoz!
Aku ditarik masuk ke vektor baru!
Sono stato tirato dentro a un nuovo vettore!
引き込まれている 新しいベクトルに！
새 벡터로 빨려들어간다!
Jestem wciągany do nowego wektora!
Sunt înăuntru la un nou vector!
Меня втягивают на новый вектор!
Ben çekiliyorum yeni bir vektöre!
- [Ethan] I am being pulled in to a new vector!
- [Ethan] Ich werde in einen neuen Vektor gezogen!
- [Ethan] Estou sendo puxado para um novo vetor!
- [Ethan] ¡Estoy siendo jalado a un nuevo vector!
Attention, brèche dans la coque.
تحذير، خرق في البدن
Avís, fisura al buc.
警告，船體破壞。
Varování, porušení trupu.
Προειδοποίηση, ρήξη κύτους.
Figyelmeztetés, hajótörés.
Peringatan, pelanggaran lambung.
Attenzione, violazione dello scafo.
警告、船体破損。
[경고, 선체 손상]
Ostrzeżenie, naruszenie kadłuba.
Avertizare, violare a corpului.
Предупреждение, пробоина на корпусе.
Uyarı, gövde ihlali.
- [Computer] Warning, hull breach.
- [Computer] Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
- [Computador] Atenção, violação do casco.
- [Computadora] Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
تحذير، خرق في البدن
Avís, fisura al buc.
警告，船體破壞
Varování, porušení trupu
Προειδοποίηση, ρήξη κύτους
Figyelmeztetés, hajótörés
Peringatan, pelanggaran lambung kapal
Attenzione, violazione dello scafo
警告、船体破損。
[경고, 선체 손상]
Ostrzeżenie, naruszenie kadłuba
Avertizare, violare a corpului
Предупреждение, пробоина
Uyarı, gövde ihlali
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning.
Warnung.
Atenção.
Advertencia.
(metal groaning) (engine whining)
(spaceship whooshing)
تحذير، خرق في البدن
Avís, fisura al buc.
警告，船體破壞
Varování, porušení trupu
Προειδοποίηση, ρήξη κύτους
Figyelmeztetés, hajótörés
Peringatan, pelanggaran lambung kapal
Attenzione, violazione dello scafo
警告、船体破損。
[경고, 선체 손상]
Ostrzeżenie, naruszenie kadłuba
Avertizare, violare a corpului
Предупреждение, пробоина
Uyarı, gövde ihlali
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning.
Warnung.
Atenção.
Advertencia.
(ethereal music) (spaceship rumbling)
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning, hull breach.
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Donnez-moi quelque chose. Où est notre vaisseau ?
أحتاج لمعلومات. هيا. أين طائرنا؟
Necessito informació. Vinga, gent! On és la nau?
我需要信息。 人們，加油！我們的鳥在哪裡？
Potřebuji informace. Lidé, pojď! Kde je náš pták?
Χρειάζομαι πληροφορίες. Ελάτε όλοι ! Πού είναι το σκάφος μας;
Szükségem van információra. Az emberek! Hol van a madár?
Aku butuh informasi. Teman-teman, ayolah! Di mana burung kita?
Ho bisogno di informazioni Gente, andiamo! Dov'è il nostro uccello?
情報が足りない！ 私達の鳥は今どこにあるの！
정보가 하나도 없잖아, 다들! 얘 어디로 갔어?
Potrzebuję informacji. Chodźcie! Gdzie jest nasz ptaszek?
Am nevoie de informații. Oameni, haide! Unde este pasărea noastră?
Мне нужна информация Люди, давай! Где наша птица?
Bilgiye ihtiyacım var. Millet, hadi! Kuşumuz nerede?
- I need information people, come on!
- Ich brauche Informationen, Leute, kommt schon!
- Eu preciso de informação pessoal, vamos lá!
- ¡Necesito información gente, vamos!
Where's our bird?
Wo ist unser Vogel?
Cadê o nosso pássaro?
¿Donde está nuestra ave?
- Gone, I mean gone.
- Weg, ich meine weg.
- Sumiu.
- Se fue, en realidad se fue.
Disparu, totalement. On n'a aucun vecteur.
ذهب. أعني، رحل. لا متجه ولاشيء لنتعقبه.
Se n'ha anat. Vull dir, ja no hi és. No hi ha cap vector, res per fer-ne un seguiment.
不見了。我的意思是，走了。 沒有矢量，沒有跟踪。
Pryč. Chci říct, pryč. Žádný vektor, nic, co by bylo možné sledovat.
Χάθηκε. Θέλω να πω, πάει. Δεν βλέπω διάνυσμα, τίποτε προς παρακολούθηση.
Elment. Úgy értem, elment. Nincs vektor, semmi követendő.
Hilang. Maksudku, pergi. Tidak ada vektor, tidak ada yang dilacak.
Andato. Voglio dire, andato. Nessun vettore, niente da tracciare.
行った。つまり、なくなった。 ベクトルなし、追跡もなし。
없어졌습니다. 진짜로요. 벡터도 없고 아무런 흔적도 없습니다.
Przepadł. To znaczy, zniknął. Bez wektora, nie mogę nic namierzyć.
Plecat. Adică, plecat. Nici un vector, nimic de urmărit.
Ушел. Я имею в виду, ушел. Нет вектора, нечего отслеживать.
Gone. Yani gitti. Vektör yok, izlenecek bir şey yok.
No vector, nothing to track.
Kein Vektor, nichts zu verfolgen.
Nenhum vetor, não há nada para rastrear.
No hay vector, nada que rastrear.
We should be able to get him
Wir sollten ihn über Q Comm überall tracken können,
Nós deveríamos ser capazes de encontrá-lo
Deberíamos ser capaces de detectarlo
La communication quantique devrait fonctionner, mais rien.
يفترض أن نراه في الاتصالات الكُميّة أينما كان، ولكن لاشيء.
Hauríem de poder arribar a ell amb la comunicació Q, però res.
我們應該能夠得到他 在Q comm任何地方，但沒有。
Měli bychom ho mít všude na Q comm , ale nic.
Θα έπρεπε να μπορούμε να τον βρούμε οπουδήποτε, αλλά τίποτα.
Képesnek kell lennünk rávenni Q comm-on bárhol, de semmi.
Kita harus bisa mendapatkannya di Q comm di mana saja, tetapi tidak ada.
Dovremmo essere in grado di prenderlo su Q comm ovunque, ma niente.
私たちは彼を捉えることができるはずです しかし量子通信はどこでも使るはずですが、反応がありません。
어디 갔건 간에 Q 연결망에 떠야하는데, 아무데도 보이질 않습니다.
Powinniśmy być w stanie go namierzyć gdziekolwiek by nie był na Q-comm , ale niczego nie ma.
Ar trebui să fim capabili să-l luăm pe Q comm oriunde, dar nimic.
Мы должны быть в состоянии получить его на Q comm где угодно, но ничего.
Onu yakalayabilmeliyiz Q comm herhangi bir yerde, ama hiçbir şey.
on Q comm anywhere, but nothing.
no Q comm em qualquer lugar, mas nada.
en comunicación Q en cualquier parte, pero nada.
aber hier ist nichts.
Nous recevons une nouvelle information.
لحظة، نستقبل معلومات جديدة.
Espereu, estem rebent informació nova.
支持。 我們收到了一些新信息。
Počkat. Získáváme nové informace.
Περιμένετε. Λάβαμε κάποιες νέες πληροφορίες.
Állj. Új információkat kapunk.
Bersiap. Kami menerima beberapa informasi baru.
Pausa. Stiamo ricevendo alcune nuove informazioni.
速報です。 新しい情報が届きました。
아, 새 정보가 들어왔습니다.
Uwaga, Otrzymaliśmy nowe informacje.
Așteptare. Primiți niște informații noi.
Ожидание. Мы получаем новую информацию.
Yanında olmak. Yeni bilgiler alıyoruz.
- Stand by, we're receiving some new information.
- Moment, wir bekommen neue Informationen.
- Aguardem, estamos recebendo novas informações.
- En espera, estamos recibiendo nueva información.
Le commandant Kane semble avoir disparu.
يبدو القائد كين اختفى.
El Comandant Kane sembla haver desaparegut.
凱恩司令 似乎已經消失了。
Velitel Kane zdá se, že zmizel.
Ο Κυβερνήτης Κέιν φαίνεται ότι έχει εξαφανιστεί.
Kane parancsnok úgy tűnik, eltűnt.
Komandan Kane tampaknya telah menghilang.
Comandante Kane sembra essere scomparso.
ケイン船長が 消えたようです。
케인 함장이 실종된 것 같다는 소식입니다.
Komandor Kane wydaje się, że zniknął.
Comandantul Kane pare să fi dispărut.
Командующий Кейн кажется, исчез.
Komutan Kane kaybolmuş görünüyor.
Commander Kane seems to have disappeared.
Commander Kane scheint verschwunden zu sein.
O comandante Kane parece ter desaparecido.
El comandante Kane parece haber desaparecido.
Où est passé papa ?
أين ذهب أبي؟
On ha anat el pare?
爸爸去哪了？
Kde odešel táta?
Πού πήγε ο μπαμπάς;
Hol ment apa?
Kemana ayah pergi?
Dove è andato papà?
お父さんはどこに行ったの？
아빠 어디 갔어요?
Gdzie poszedł tata?
Unde a plecat tata?
Куда пошел папа?
Babam nereye gitti?
- Where did Dad go?
- Wo ist Dad?
- Para onde meu pai foi?
- ¿A donde fue papá?
- [Reporter] The Longshot was ready to make
- [Reporter] Die Longshot war bereit,
- [Repórter] O Longshot estava pronto para fazer
- [Reportera] El Longshot estaba listo para hacer
Le Longshot était sur le point de rentrer,
"لونج شوت" كانت على استعداد لرحلة العودة،
La Longshot estava a punt de fer el viatge de retorn a casa,
Longshot準備好了 讓回程航程回家，
Longshot byl připraven na cestu zpět domů,
Το Longshot ήταν έτοιμο να κάνει το ταξίδι της επιστροφής,
A Longshot kész volt hazatérni
The Longshot sudah siap untuk membuat perjalanan pulang ke rumah,
Il Longshot era pronto per rendere il viaggio di ritorno a casa,
ロングショット号はすでに準備を終え、すでに帰還しているはずでした
롱샷은 귀환 여정을 준비하고 있었는데
Longshot był gotowy aby wrócić do domu,
Longshot-ul era gata pentru a face călătoria de întoarcere acasă,
Longshot был готов совершить обратный рейс домой,
Longshot hazırdı dönüş yolculuğunu eve yapmak,
the return voyage home
die Rückreise anzutreten,
a viagem de regresso para casa
el viaje de regreso a casa
but something seems to have gone wrong.
aber etwas scheint schiefgelaufen zu sein.
mas algo parece ter dado errado.
pero algo parece haber salido mal.
quand une avarie semble s'être déclarée.
ولكن يبدو أن خطأ ما قد حدث.
però alguna cosa sembla haver anat malament.
但有些東西 似乎出了問題。
ale zdá se, že se něco pokazilo.
αλλά κάτι φαίνεται ότι έχει πάει στραβά.
de valami úgy tűnik, rosszul ment.
tapi sesuatu tampaknya salah.
ma qualcosa sembra essere andato storto.
しかし何か うまくいかなかったようです。
무언가 문제가 생긴 모양입니다.
ale wydaje się, że coś poszło nie tak.
dar ceva pare să fi greșit.
но что-то кажется, пошло не так.
ama bazı şeyler yanlış gitti gibi görünüyor.
We will continue to follow the story
Wir werden die Story weiter verfolgen
Continuaremos a seguir esta história com outras
Continuaremos siguiendo la historia
Nous reprendrons l'antenne
سنتابع الأخبار أولاً بأول
Continuarem seguint la història
我們將繼續關注這個故事
Budeme pokračovat v příběhu
Θα συνεχίσουμε να παρακολουθούμε την ιστορία
Továbbra is követjük a történetet
Kami akan terus mengikuti kabarnya
Continueremo a seguire la storia
私たちは今回の事故を追い続けます
새 소식이 들어오는 대로
Nadal będziemy śledzić tą historię
Vom continua să urmărim povestea
Мы продолжим следить за историей
Hikayeyi takip etmeye devam edeceğiz
and provide updates on any new developments.
und Updates zu neuen Entwicklungen liefern.
atualizações sobre quaisquer novidades.
y trayendo actualizaciones de cualquier nuevo desarrollo.
dès que nous aurons davantage d'information.
ونخبركم بأي مستجدات وتطورات.
i proporcionant-los actualitzacions sobre qualsevol novetat.
並提供更新 在任何新的發展。
a poskytovat informace o jakémkoli novém vývoji.
και θα σας ενημερώνουμε για κάθε νέα εξέλιξη.
és frissítéseket új fejleményekről.
dan memberikan pembaruan pada perkembangan baru.
e fornire aggiornamenti su eventuali nuovi sviluppi.
そして続報が入り次第 順次お伝えしていきます。
계속해서 전해드리도록 하겠습니다.
i poinformujemy o wszelkich nowych wydarzeniach.
și să furnizeze actualizări cu privire la orice evoluții noi.
и предоставлять обновления на любые новые разработки.
ve güncellemeler sağlamak herhangi bir yeni gelişme üzerine.
(tense music)
- [Computer] Warning, hull breach.
- [Computer] Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
- [Computador] Atenção, violação do casco.
- [Computadora] Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Premier contact.
الاتصال الأول "في الخيال العلمي: الاتصال الأول كناية عن أول اتصال بكائنات من الفضاء، على الأغلب تكون عاقلة"
Primer contacte.
第一次接觸。
První kontakt.
Πρώτη επαφή.
Első találkozás.
Pertemuan pertama.
Primo contatto.
ファーストコンタクト…
첫 조우로군.
Pierwszy kontakt.
Primul contact.
Первый контакт.
İlk temas.
- A first contact.
- Ein erster Kontakt.
- Um primeiro contato.
- Un primer contacto.
Okay, way above my pay grade.
Okay, das überschreitet meine Kompetenzen.
Ok, bem acima do meu salário.
Okay, esto está muy por arriba de mi paga.
D'accord, d'accord, ça me dépasse.
حسناً، حسناً، هذا أعلى من مرتبي الوظيفي.
D'acord, bé, no em paguen prou per això.
好的，好吧，高於我的工資等級。
Ok,ok, dost nad mým platovým stupněm.
Ναί, εντάξει, μα δεν πληρώνομαι για κάτι τέτοιο.
Oké, oké, a fizetési osztályom felett.
Oke, oke, di atas nilai gajiku.
Ok, ok, sopra il mio voto di paga.
ok、ok、これも仕事の内だ。
좋아, 좋아, 추가 수당을 받아야겠는데.
Ok, ok. To przekracza moje kompetencje.
Bine, bine, deasupra gradului meu de salarizare.
Хорошо, хорошо, выше моего уровня оплаты.
Tamam, tamam, maaşımın üstünde.
- [Computer] Warning, hull breach.
- [Computer] Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
- [Computador] Atenção, violação do casco.
- [Computadora] Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning, hull breach. (glass cracking)
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
Warning, hull breach. (metal groaning)
Warnung, Rumpf durchbrochen.
Aviso, violação do casco.
Advertencia, brecha en el casco.
(sad music) (glass cracking)
(aliens buzzing)
(metal groaning)
21 HEURES PLUS TARD
2 Stunden später
Après une journée depuis sa dernière communication,
بعد ما يقارب اليوم من آخر اتصال،
Després de gairebé un dia des de la seva última comunicació,
差不多一天后 自從他上次溝通以來
Po téměř jednom dni od jeho poslední komunikace,
Μια μέρα σχεδόν μετά από την τελευταία επικοινωνία του,
Majdnem egy nap után az utolsó kommunikáció óta
Setelah hampir sehari sejak komunikasi terakhirnya,
Dopo quasi un giorno dalla sua ultima comunicazione,
彼との更新が途絶えてから一日が経過しました、
그의 마지막 통신으로부터 거의 하루가 지났습니다.
Po prawie dobie od jego ostatniego komunikatu,
După aproape o zi de la ultima sa comunicare,
После почти дня с момента его последнего общения,
Neredeyse bir gün sonra Son iletişiminden beri
- [Reporter] After almost a day
- [Reporter] Nach fast einem Tag
- [Repórter] Depois de quase um dia
- [Reportera] Después de casi un día
since his last communication,
seit seiner letzten Kommunikation
desde sua última comunicação,
desde su última comunicación,
nous sommes toujours à la recherche du commandant Kane.
البحث عن القائد كين لا يزال سارياً.
la recerca del Comandant Kane continua.
搜索 凱恩指揮官繼續說道。
výzkum pro velitele Kana pokračuje.
η αναζήτηση για τον κυβερνήτη Κέιν συνεχίζεται.
a keresés Kane parancsnok folytatódik.
pencarian untuk Komandan Kane berlanjut.
la ricerca per il comandante Kane continua.
케인 함장을 찾기 위한 노력은 계속됩니다.
poszukiwania komandorar Kane'a nadal trwają.
cautarea pentru comandantul Kane continuă.
Поиск для командира Кейн продолжается.
Araştırma Komutan Kane için devam ediyor.
ケイン船長の捜索は未だ続けられています。
the search for Commander Kane continues.
geht die Suche nach Commander Kane weiter.
a busca pelo Comandante Kane continua.
la búsqueda del Comandante Kane continúa.
Nous avons contacté
We have reached out for the Commander's family for comment.
Wir haben die Familie des Commanders kontaktiert.
Entramos em contato com a família do Comandante.
Hemos llamado a la familia del Comandante por comentarios.
نحن نحاول التواصل
Hem intentat d'aconseguir
我們已經伸出手
Našli jsme se
Πάμε να βρούμε
Megérkeztünk
Kami telah menjangkau
Abbiamo raggiunto
또한 케인 함장의 가족에게
Zwróciliśmy się
Ne-am întors
Мы достигли
Ulaştık
司令官の家族のために コメントをお願いします。
la famille du commandant.
مع عائلة القائد للتعليق.
declaracions de la família del comandant.
為指揮官的家人 徵求意見
pro rodinu velitele pro komentář.
την οικογένεια του Κυβερνήτη για κάποιο σχόλιο.
a parancsnok családjához megjegyzést.
untuk keluarga Komandan untuk komentar.
per la famiglia del comandante per un commento
이 소식을 전했는데요.
do rodziny komandora aby uzyskać komentarz.
pentru familia comandantului pentru comentarii.
для семьи командира для комментариев.
Komutanın ailesi için yorum için.
We're sure it's been a difficult time for them.
Wir sind sicher, dass es eine schwierige Zeit für sie ist.
Temos certeza que tem sido um momento difícil para eles.
Estamos seguros de que ha sido un tiempo difícil para ellos.
Ce sont des moments forcément difficiles pour eux.
نحن على يقين أن هذا الوقت عصيب عليهم.
Estem segurs que és un moment difícil per a ells.
我們確信它已經存在 他們很難過。
Jsme si jisti, že to bylo pro ně těžké.
Είμαστε βέβαιοι ότι είναι πολύ δύσκολες στιγμές γι 'αυτούς.
Biztosak vagyunk benne nehéz ideje számukra.
Kami yakin sudah waktu yang sulit bagi mereka.
Siamo sicuri che sia stato un momento difficile per loro.
私たちは彼が発見されると信じています
가족들에게도 힘든 시간일 것입니다.
Jesteśmy pewni, że to trudny dla nich czas.
Suntem siguri că a fost un moment dificil pentru ei.
Мы уверены, что это было трудное время для них.
Olduğundan eminiz onlar için zor bir zaman.
Along with the rest of the world,
Zusammen mit dem Rest der Welt
Junto com o resto do mundo,
Junto con el resto del mundo,
Le monde entier espère son retour indemne.
إضافة مع باقي العالم، كلنا نأمل بعودة سليمة للقائد.
Juntament amb la resta del món, tots desitgem un retorn segur.
與世界其他地方一樣， 我們現在都希望安全返回。
Spolu se zbytkem světa, všichni nyní doufáme, že se vrátí bezpečně.
Όλοι οι άνθρωποι, μπορούμε μόνο να ελπίζουμε να τα καταφέρει και να γυρίσει ασφαλής.
A világ többi részével együtt mindannyian reméljük, hogy biztonságosan visszatérünk.
Seiring dengan sisa dunia, kita semua sekarang mengharapkan pengembalian yang aman.
Insieme al resto del mondo, ora speriamo tutti in un ritorno sicuro.
世界の他の国々と一緒に、 私達全員は今彼の安全な帰還を望んでいます。
전 세계가 모두 그의 무사 귀환을 바라고 있습니다.
Wraz z resztą świata wszyscy mamy nadzieję na jego bezpieczny powrót.
Împreună cu restul lumii, toți sperăm acum să ne întoarcem în siguranță.
Вместе с остальным миром, теперь мы все надеемся на безопасное возвращение.
Dünyanın geri kalanıyla birlikte, şimdi hepimiz güvenli bir dönüş için umut ediyoruz.
we hold out hope for a safe return.
hoffen wir auf eine sichere Rückkehr.
nós esperamos por um retorno seguro.
esperamos un regreso seguro.
Assez pour aujourd'hui.
لا مزيد لنعمله اليوم.
Avui no podem fer res més.
今天沒什麼可做的。
Nic víc dělat dnes nemužem.
Δυστυχώς δεν μπορούμε να κάνουμε τίποτα άλλο σήμερα.
Ma semmi több.
Tidak ada lagi yang bisa dilakukan hari ini.
Niente di più da fare oggi.
今日はもうできることは無いわ。
오늘은 할 일이 없네.
Nic więcej dzisiaj nie zrobimy
Nimic altceva de făcut astăzi.
Больше нечего делать сегодня.
Bugün yapacak daha fazla bir şey yok.
- [Sarah] Nothing more to do today.
- [Sarah] Heute können wir nichts mehr machen.
- [Sarah] Não há nada mais a fazer hoje.
- [Sarah] Nada mas que hacer hoy.
Rentrez.
عُد للمنزل.
Ves a casa.
回家。
Jdi domů.
Πηγαίνετε σπίτι.
Hazamenni.
Pulang ke rumah.
Andare a casa.
帰りましょう。
퇴근하게.
Idź do domu.
Du-te acasă.
Иди домой.
Eve git.
Go home.
Gehen Sie nach Hause.
Vá para casa.
Ve a casa.
(radio squelching)
- Uh, Flight?
- Äh, Flight?
- Vôo?
- Uh, ¿Vuelo?
Contrôle ?
مركز القيادة؟
Control?
飛行？
Κέντρο ;
Repülési?
Penerbangan?
Volo?
フライト？
어, 플라이트?
Kontrola?
Zbor?
Рейс?
Uçuş?
Flight?
Je vois quelque chose.
هناك شيئ ما.
Hi ha alguna cosa.
有一些東西。
Κάτι συμβαίνει.
Van valami.
Ada sesuatu.
C'è qualcosa.
何かがあります。
여기 뭔가...
Tam coś jest.
Este ceva.
Есть что-то.
Birşey var.
Je tu něco.
There's something.
Da ist etwas.
Há alguma coisa.
Hay algo.
- [Ethan] Control, come in.
- [Ethan] Control, bitte kommen.
- [Ethan] Controle, responda.
- [Ethan] Control, entra.
Contrôle, à vous.
Ovládej, pojď.
مركز التحكم، أجب.
Control, canvi.
控制，進來。
Κέντρο, έλα.
Ellenőrzés, gyere be.
Kontrol, masuk.
Controllo, entra.
制御してください。
관제실, 응답하라
Kontrola, zgłoś się.
Controlează, intră.
Контроль, заходи.
Kontrol, içeri gel.
Vous voyez ça ?
أنتم هناك هل ترون ذلك؟
Ho heu sentit?
你們得到這個嗎？
Chápete to?
Εσείς παιδιά το βλέπετε αυτό;
Ezt kaptad?
Kalian mendapatkan ini?
Ragazzi, avete capito?
다들 이거 들려?
Odbieracie to?
Voi obtineti asta?
Вы, ребята, получаете это?
Bunu anladınız mı?
あなたはこれを受信したの？
- You guys getting this?
- Hört ihr mich?
- Vocês estão recebendo isso?
- ¿Chicos están escuchando esto?
NORADが異常を報告しています ISSから約2.5クリック。
Le NORAD a détecté une anomalie à 2,5 km de l'ISS.
- [NavCom] NORAD is reporting an anomaly
- [NavCom] NORAD berichtet eine Abnormität
- [NavCom] NORAD está relatando uma anomalia
- [NavCom] NORAD está reportando una anomalía
نوراد تبلغ عن شذوذ على بعد ٢.٥كم من المحطة الدولية "نوراد: قيادة الدفاع الفضائي الشمال أمريكية"
El NORAD està informant d'una anomalia aproximadament a 2,5 clics de l'EEI.
NORAD正在報告一個異常現象 來自國際空間站的大約2.5次點擊。
NORAD hlásí anomálii přibližně 2,5 kliku od ISS.
Το NORAD αναφέρει μια ανωμαλία περίπου 2,5 κλικ από τον διαστημικό σταθμό ISS.
A NORAD anomáliáról számol be körülbelül 2,5 kattintás az ISS-től.
NORAD melaporkan anomali sekitar 2,5 klik dari ISS.
Il NORAD sta segnalando un'anomalia circa 2,5 clic dalla ISS.
NORAD가 국제 우주 정거장에서 2.5범위 떨어진 곳의 이상 현상을 포착했습니다.
NORAD zgłasza anomalię około 2,5 klików od ISS.
NORAD raportează o anomalie aproximativ 2,5 clicuri de la ISS.
NORAD сообщает об аномалии примерно 2,5 клика с МКС.
NORAD bir anomali rapor ediyor ISS'den yaklaşık 2,5 tıklama.
approximately 2.4 clicks from ISS.
bei etwa 2,4 Clicks von der ISS.
há aproximadamente 2,4 cliques do ISS.
aproximadamente de 2.4 clics del ISS.
C'est-à-dire ? On a un visuel ?
「異常」？映像はある？
شذوذ؟ هل لدينا رؤية؟
"Anomalia"? Tenim contacte visual?
“異常”？我們有視覺嗎？
"Anomálie"? Máme obraz?
"Ανωμαλία"; Έχουμε εικόνα ;
"Anomália"? Van egy vizuális?
"Anomali"? Apakah kita punya visual?
"Anomalia"? Abbiamo un visual?
이상 현상? 화면 띄울 수 있나?
"Anomalia"? Czy mamy obraz?
"Anomalie"? Avem o viziune?
«Аномалия»? У нас есть визуал?
"Anomali"? Görselimiz var mı?
- Anomaly?
- Abnormität?
- Anomalia?
- ¿Anomalía?
Do we have a visual?
Können wir etwas sehen?
Nós temos imagens?
¿Tenemos visual?
- Coming up.
- Kommt sofort.
- Entrando agora.
- Ahí va.
Imminent.
قادمة.
Ara vaig.
接下來。
Přichází.
'Ερχεται
Következik.
Akan datang.
Venendo
来ます。
곧 됩니다.
Nadchodzi.
Urmează.
Подходит.
Geliyor.
(dramatic music)
Qu'est-ce que c'est ?
ماهذا؟
Què és això?
那是什麼？
Co to je?
Τι είναι αυτό ;
Mi az?
Apa itu?
Cos'è quello?
あれは一体何？
저게 뭐지?
Co to jest?
Ce este asta?
Что это такое?
O nedir?
- What is that?
- Was ist das?
- O que é isso?
- ¿Que es eso?
(aliens whizzing)
Vous les suivez ?
هل تتابع؟
Ho estàs seguint?
你在追踪嗎？
Sledujete?
Το παρακολουθείτε;
Nyomon követ?
Apakah kau melacak?
Stai seguendo?
追跡できてる？
추적하고 있나?
Śledzisz to?
Urmăriți?
Вы отслеживаете?
İzliyor musun
Can you track?
Können Sie es tracken?
Você pode rastrear?
¿Puedes rastrear?
- I don't.
- Eu não.
- No puedo.
- Nein.
(air whooshing)
- [Abby] Jack!
- [Abby] ¡Jack!
جاك!
Jack!
插口！
Τζάκ !
Jack!
Mendongkrak!
ジャック！
잭!
Jack!
Джек!
¡Jack!
(aliens buzzing)
- [Jack] Whoa.
- [Jack] Oha.
- [Jack] Uau.
- [Sarah] Whoa.
(Ethan gasps)
(dramatic music)
Papa !
أبي!
Papa!
爸爸！
Tatínek!
Πατερούλη !
Apu!
Ayah!
Papà!
パパ！
아빠!
Tatuś!
Tati!
Папа!
Baba!
Daddy!
Pai!
¡Papi!
C'est moi...
إنه أنا...
Soc jo...
是我...
To jsem já...
Εγώ είμαι...
Én vagyok...
Ini aku...
Sono io...
俺だよ…
왔어...
To ja...
Sunt eu...
Это я...
Benim...
- It's me, it's me!
- Ich bin es, ich bin es!
- Sou eu, sou eu!
- ¡Soy yo, soy yo!
C'est moi !
إنه أنا!
Soc jo!
是我！
To jsem já!
Εγώ είμαι !
Én vagyok!
Ini aku!
Sono io!
俺なんだよ
왔어, 여보.
To ja!
Sunt eu!
Это я!
Benim!
(Abby sobbing)
(sullen music)